On the eve of their Sweet 16 matchup, a Los Angeles Times article by Ben Boll
labeled the UCLA Bruins as America's Sweethearts and the LSU Tigers as basketball villains and
dirty debutantes. You can criticize coaches all you want, but the one thing I'm not going to let
you do, I'm not going to let you attack young people. It was so sexist and they don't even
know it. Dirty debutantes? Are you kidding me? It brings me back to Don Imus when he,
you know, talked about the quote-unquote nappy-headed hoes. Now, the writer has since issued an
apology, but it's already said. You know what I'm saying? Like, I get the apology thing,
but you already put it out. And it wasn't just sexist, it was racist. That part right there.
You know, and the Washington Post had also profiled the LSU women's basketball head coach,
Kim Mulkey. You know, and they painted her as a whole polarizing figure for being brash and whatnot.
I feel like a lot of the things that were levied against her were really just about her being a
quote-unquote straight shooter, which is what they would call her if she was a man.
Now, there are other issues that people have with like, oh, she's, they say that she's a
MAGA supporter, et cetera. You know what really matters ultimately? Do her players feel safe with
her? You know, does she treat her players with any level of discrimination? I think it says volumes
that she has a whole team of sisters and they seem to have no issue with her.
I wish she would have called out that racism when she was talking though.
Well, you know, she said that the person couldn't even see the sexism. And I think a lot of white
people can't see the racism. And for what it's worth, Dirty Debutant is code for nappy-headed hoes.
He might as well have just said these DEI basketball players.
Right?
Because they're the same language.
We are, we are, we are.